<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <div class="topic" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:mtps="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/mtps" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:cs="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/">
    
    <!--Published via DxPublisher.-->
    <div id="mainSection">
      <div id="mainBody">
        <p>A Web Site is the host for a web application running in the cloud that you can control and manage. After you create a Web Site you can start, stop, and delete it whenever you need to. You can access the web site as easily as you access a web site hosted on a computer in your office.</p>
        <p>
					Web Sites provides the ability to quickly and easily create and deploy web sites with support for multiple application frameworks and preloaded with popular open source applications.</p>
        <p>To create a new Web Site, click the <strong>New</strong> icon, click <strong>Web Site</strong>, and then follow the instructions for <strong>Quick Create</strong>, <strong>From Gallery</strong>, or <strong>Custom Create</strong>.</p>
        <a id="QuickCreate">
          <!---->
        </a>
        <h2 class="heading">Using Quick Create</h2>
        <div id="sectionSection0" class="section">
          <p>Quick Create is the fastest method for creating a website, requiring only that you provide a URL. <strong>Quick Create</strong> doesn’t give you options for setting up a database, so consider using <strong>Quick Create</strong> when you don’t need database connectivity or plan to setup a database later.</p>
        </div>
        <h2 class="heading">Using From Gallery</h2>
        <div id="sectionSection1" class="section">
          <p>Create a web site <strong>From Gallery</strong> when you want to quickly build a web site from a template. When you create a web site <strong>From Gallery</strong> you can have a web site up and running almost instantly.</p>
        </div>
        <h2 class="heading">Using Custom Create</h2>
        <div id="sectionSection2" class="section">
          <p>Choose to <strong>Custom Create</strong> a Web Site when you want to create your website and other resources that you would like to use with your website simultaneously. This includes such things as setting up a database to use along with your site.</p>
        </div>
      </div>
      <p>
        <!---->
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>