<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <div class="topic" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:mtps="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/mtps" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:cs="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/">
    
    <!--Published via DxPublisher.-->
    <div id="mainSection">
      <div id="mainBody">
        <p>Monitor a web site to get an idea of web site performance and determine the rate at which the web site is sending out various Http status code messages.</p>
        <div id="sectionSection0" class="section">
          <p>The chart on the <strong>Monitor</strong> page can be configured to display up to 6 different metrics at a time. These metrics include web site performance data and the rate at which the web site sends out certain Http status code messages. The following metrics can be displayed on the <strong>Monitor</strong> page chart:</p>
          <ul>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>CPUTime</strong> - a measure of the web site’s CPU usage in terms of milliseconds, not percentage. This relates to the <strong>CPU TIME</strong> quota displayed on the <strong>Dashboard</strong> page.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Requests</strong> - a count of client requests to the web site.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Data Out</strong> – bytes of data sent by the web site to clients.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Data In</strong> - bytes of data received by the web site from clients.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http Client Errors</strong> - number of Http “4xx Client Error” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http Server Errors</strong> - number of Http “5xx Server Error” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http Successes</strong> - number of Http “2xx Success” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http Redirects</strong> - number of Http “3xx Redirection” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http 401 errors</strong> - number of Http “401 Unauthorized” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http 403 errors</strong> - number of Http “403 Forbidden” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http 404 errors</strong> - number of Http “404 Not Found” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Http 406 errors</strong> - number of Http “406 Not Acceptable” messages sent.<br /><br /></li>
          </ul>
          <p>To add a metric to the chart simply click to select the icon that represents the metric. To remove the metric from the chart, click to deselect the icon for the metric.</p>
          <p>If you determine from viewing chart metrics that performance is unacceptable or that the web site is generating an unexpected number of particular Http status code messages, consider enabling diagnostics from the Web Site’s <strong>Configure</strong> page.</p>
          <p>The chart can be configured to display absolute or relative values of the metrics monitored for periods of time ranging from 6 hours to 1 day to 1 week.</p>
          <div class="alert">
            <table>
              <tr>
                <th align="left">
                  <img src="/HelpContent/GetImage/websiteextension/jj205506.note(en-us,MSDN.10).gif" class="mtpsimage" alt="note" xmlns="" />Note </th>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td>
						A chart similar to this chart is displayed on the <strong>Dashboard</strong> page.<p><!----></p></td>
              </tr>
            </table>
            <p>
              <!---->
            </p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
      <p>
        <!---->
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>