<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <div class="topic" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:mtps="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/mtps" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:cs="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/">
    
    <!--Published via DxPublisher.-->
    <div id="mainSection">
      <div id="mainBody">
        <p>Web site configuration options govern several web application specific settings, the type and level of diagnostic logging that is employed and any alternative hostnames used to connect to the web site.</p>
        <div id="sectionSection0" class="section">
          <p>The following configuration options can be set for a web site from web site’s <strong>Configure</strong> management page:</p>
          <ul>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>framework</strong> - Set the version of .NET framework or PHP required by your web application.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>domain names</strong> - View additional domain names for the web site here. Additional domain names can be added to the web site by clicking the <strong>Manage Domains</strong> icon at the bottom of the page.<br /><br /><div class="alert"><table><tr><th align="left"><img src="/HelpContent/GetImage/websiteextension/jj205510.note(en-us,MSDN.10).gif" class="mtpsimage" alt="note" xmlns="" />Note </th></tr><tr><td>
								Depending on your plan and scale mode you may not be able to add custom domain names to your web site. If the <strong>Manage Domains</strong> command is greyed out try moving your web site from <strong>Intro Shared</strong> to <strong>Basic Shared</strong> or<strong> Reserved</strong> on the <strong>Scale</strong> page<p><!----></p></td></tr></table><p><!----></p></div></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>diagnostics</strong> - Set options for gathering diagnostic information for your web site including:<br /><br /><ul><li class="unordered"><strong>Web Server Logging</strong> - Specify to record all HTTP transactions using the <a href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=90561" class="mtpslink" target="_blank">W3C extended log file format</a>.<br /><br /></li><li class="unordered"><strong>Detailed Error Messages</strong> - Specify whether to log detailed error messages for the web site.<br /><br /></li><li class="unordered"><strong>Failed Request Tracing</strong> - Specify whether to enable failed request tracing.<br /><br /></li></ul><div class="alert"><table><tr><th align="left"><img src="/HelpContent/GetImage/websiteextension/jj205510.note(en-us,MSDN.10).gif" class="mtpsimage" alt="note" xmlns="" />Note </th></tr><tr><td>
								For more information about web site’s diagnostics and logging see <a href="http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=248086" class="mtpslink" target="_blank">Reading Log Files from a Web Site</a>.<p><!----></p></td></tr></table><p><!----></p></div></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>App Settings</strong> - Specify name/value pairs that will be loaded by your web site on start up. For .NET sites, these settings will be injected into your .NET configuration <strong>AppSettings</strong> at runtime, overriding existing settings. For PHP sites these settings will be available as environment variables at runtime.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Connection Strings</strong> - View connection strings for linked resources. For .NET sites, these connection strings will be injected into your .NET configuration <strong>connectionStrings</strong> settings at runtime, overriding existing entries where the key equals the connection string name. For PHP sites these settings will be available as environment variables at runtime.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Default Documents</strong> - Add your web site’s default documents to this list if it is not already in the list. Rearrange the order of the list as needed.<br /><br /></li>
            <li class="unordered">
              <strong>Handler Mappings</strong> - Specify a custom script processor executable to handle requests for the specified file extension type by providing a path for the custom script relative to the web site ftp root directory. Optional arguments can also be provided if needed.<br /><br /></li>
          </ul>
        </div>
      </div>
      <p>
        <!---->
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>