<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <div class="topic" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:mtps="http://msdn2.microsoft.com/mtps" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:cs="http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/">
    
    <!--Published via DxPublisher.-->
    <div id="mainSection">
      <div id="mainBody">
        <p>Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure (HTTPS) allows your website to provide secure connections over the web to clients accessing your website. Traffic over HTTPS is secure and encrypted and prevents outsiders from reading packets sent between your website and the client.</p>
        <p>
          <strong>Subscription Support</strong> - Depending on the plan your website is provisioned against, you may have the ability to activate HTTPS on your website. Please check your plan to determine if your web site is eligible for HTTPS. You can verify if your website is eligible for HTTPS by clicking the <strong>Certificates</strong> tab. If you see the following message “SSL is not enabled for this web site” then you cannot use this feature. Sometimes scaling your website from <strong>Intro Shared</strong> to <strong>Basic Shared</strong> or <strong>Reserved</strong> from the web site’s <strong>Scale</strong> management page will provide access to this feature.</p>
        <p>
          <strong>SSL Information</strong> - Web Sites supports two flavors of SSL:</p>
        <ol class="ordered">
          <li>
            <strong>TCP/IP Based SSL</strong> – IP based SSL is the traditional flavor of SSL that works by binding an SSL certificate to the IP address of a web site. This version of SSL works on all browsers but requires a web site to be bound to a unique IP address.<br /><br /></li>
          <li>
            <strong>Server Name Indication (SNI) SSL</strong> - This works by binding an SSL certificate to the host name of a web site rather than the IP address of a web site. SNI SSL works on all the latest browsers and operating systems, but clients using out-of-date browsers will not work properly with SNI SSL enabled sites.<br /><br /><div class="alert"><table><tr><th align="left"><img src="/HelpContent/GetImage/websiteextension/jj822110.note(en-us,MSDN.10).gif" class="mtpsimage" alt="note" xmlns="" />Note </th></tr><tr><td>
							SNI is supported on the following browsers: IE7+ on Windows Vista and higher, Mozilla Firefox 2.0+, Google Chrome on Windows Vista and higher, Chrome 6+ on XP, Chrome 5.0.342.1+ on OS X 10.5.7 or higher, Windows Phone 7+, MobileSafari iOS 4.0+, Android v3.x+, Opera 8.0+, Opera Mobile 10.1+, Safari 2.1+ on OS X 10.5.6 and higher.<p><!----></p></td></tr></table><p><!----></p></div></li>
        </ol>
        <p>
          <strong>Configuration</strong> - If your web site is using the default host name assigned to it when it was created, the plan might already include a default SNI SSL certificate that can be used with your site. Refer to your plan for more information. You can also determine if your web site natively supports SNI SSL by opening a browser and pointing it to https://[your default website host name]. If the web site opens then it provides support for SNI SSL.</p>
        <p>If you want to provide your own custom SSL Certificate to bind against your default or custom domain name(s) follow these steps:</p>
        <ol class="ordered">
          <li>
						Obtain an SSL Certificate from a Trusted SSL Certificate Authority (CA). Make sure this SSL Certificate is registered with the domain name of your site.<br /><br /></li>
          <li>
						If you are using a custom domain, make sure you have added this domain to your web site. To do this go to the web site’s <strong>Configure</strong> management page, click <strong>Manage Domains</strong> in the command bar and add your custom domain name.<br /><br /></li>
          <li>
						Go to the web site’s <strong>Certificates</strong> management page and click <strong>Upload Certificate</strong> in the command bar. Browse the computer and locate your SSL certificate personal information exchange (.pfx) file. This file should have been given to when you obtained the SSL certificate from your trusted SSL certificate authority (CA). Once you have located it, enter the <strong>password</strong> you used to protect your file. Click <strong>OK</strong> to upload the SSL certificate.<br /><br /></li>
          <li>
						Your new SSL Certificate is now uploaded and assigned to your domain.<br /><br /></li>
          <li>
						By default all SSL certificate are uploaded in SNI SSL mode. To change to IP based SSL mode, select the SSL certificate that you would like to work in IP based mode. In the command bar you will see <strong>Change to IP Based</strong>, click this command to put the web site in IP based SSL mode for this certificate. An IP address will then be assigned to your site and this SSL Certificate will be bound to it.<br /><br /><div class="alert"><table><tr><th align="left"><img src="/HelpContent/GetImage/websiteextension/jj822110.Important(en-us,MSDN.10).gif" class="mtpsimage" alt="Important" xmlns="" />Important </th></tr><tr><td>
							Changing a web site’s SSL mode from SNI SSL to IP based SSL may result in charges. Check details of your plan before changing a web site’s SSL mode from SNI SSL to IP based SSL.<p><!----></p></td></tr></table><p><!----></p></div></li>
        </ol>
        <div id="sectionSection0" class="section">
          <p>
            <!---->
          </p>
        </div>
      </div>
      <p>
        <!---->
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>